06/06/19 10:19 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="445" phase="goal_identification">hi [Name], thank you for your interest! Please reply &quot;yes&quot; if you receive this message.</goal_setting> 

06/06/19 10:21 Patient: Yes 

06/06/19 10:46 Coach: To repeat: the goal for this week is to walk 2,000 steps per day every day from Monday - Saturday. And you feel this goal is 100% attainable. We will also use the first week to see how much you are walking and to adjust to the program. 

06/06/19 10:46 Coach: My name is [Name] and I am excited to be working with you! Have a great day! 

06/06/19 10:48 Patient: Thank you [Name] I am so excited

06/06/19 12:19 Patient: Hey [Name] this is [Name] just letting you know I have someone want to sign up for the Fitbit

06/06/19 12:23 Coach: Hi [Name], that&apos;s great!! Thank&apos;s for looking for us. Would you be able to give them my cell phone number? It is [Phone]. They can call me and I can touch base with them. 

06/06/19 12:24 Coach: <goal_action gate:gateId="446" phase="follow up">By the way, I just took a look and you&apos;re past your goal for today already! Great job!</goal_action> 

06/06/19 12:25 Patient: That&apos;s good 

06/06/19 12:48 Coach: Thank you again [Name]! 

06/07/19 08:49 Coach: Good morning [Name]. Great job on your steps yesterday -  you walked over 2,500! Keep it up today!

06/07/19 09:23 Patient: Good morning [Name] ok thanks 

06/07/19 14:19 Coach: Hi [Name], I&apos;m not seeing any steps for today. Are you wearing your fitbit? If so, could you try to sync it? You can sync it by going into the app and then just pulling the screen down. 

06/07/19 15:18 Patient: I do have it on 

06/07/19 15:29 Coach: Hmm. I don&apos;t see is syncing yet. 

06/07/19 15:30 Coach: When you get a chance, could you open the Fitbit app and find the picture of your &quot;charge 2 fitbit&quot;? Then touch the picture of your Fitbit device at the top of the screen and pull down.

06/07/19 21:20 Coach: Hi [Name], I see that your fitbit synced and I&apos;m floored -  You actually walked over 9,000 steps yesterday and over 12,000 steps today!! Incredible!! Keep up the amazing job!

06/10/19 09:42 Coach: Good morning [Name]! Would you prefer to set up new goal on Mondays (today) at the beginning of the week, or would you prefer Thursdays? We also wait until next Monday if you prefer. 

06/10/19 09:50 Patient: Good morning! We can wait for next Monday I prefer

06/10/19 09:54 Coach: Okay sounds good :) 

06/12/19 20:44 Coach: Hi [Name]! Great job with your fitbit steps the last couple of days - all over 7,000! I&apos;ll check back in with you again on Friday. Keep it up!

06/14/19 08:52 Coach: Hi [Name], how has your first full week been? You&apos;re doing amazing! 

06/14/19 08:55 Patient: Hi [Name] it&apos;s doing great 👍🏼 

06/17/19 09:47 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="447" phase="goal_identification">Good morning [Name]! It&apos;s Monday and time to set up your 2nd SMART goal. What would you like your goal to be this week? Remember, we want it to be something that you are 100% confident you can attain.</goal_setting> 

06/17/19 13:19 Patient: Good afternoon [Name] !We can set up new goal.ok 100%

06/17/19 13:21 Coach: Great! What would you like your week 2 goal be? It looks like there were some days with a lot of steps and others with less. 

06/17/19 13:23 Patient: Let&apos;s do 100%this week 

06/17/19 14:10 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="448" phase="goal_refining">Okay! So does that mean 2,000 steps/day - did you want to still keep it Monday - Saturday, or do Monday - Friday instead?</goal_setting>

06/17/19 14:11 Patient: No Monday-Friday 

06/17/19 14:13 Coach: Great! Okay to reiterate: your 2nd week SMART goal will be 2,000 steps/day Monday - Friday. I&apos;ll check in with you later this week. Keep up the amazing work! 

06/17/19 14:15 Patient: Tuesday be good for me to start,because I&apos;m not at my best today sick 

06/17/19 14:16 Coach: Oh no! I&apos;m sorry to hear that you&apos;re not doing well! Sure no problem, lets start tomorrow :) Feel better soon [Name]! 

06/17/19 14:16 Patient: Ok thanks 🙏 

06/18/19 19:05 Coach: <goal_action gate:gateId="449" phase="follow up">Hi [Name], great job on getting those steps in today!</goal_action> 

06/18/19 19:06 Patient: Thank you [Name] 

06/20/19 08:41 Coach: Great job with over 12,000 steps yesterday! 

06/20/19 08:41 Coach: Two more days for this week! 

06/20/19 08:42 Patient: Ok thanks 

06/21/19 18:01 Coach: Hi [Name], just wanted to say great job for the second week!! Did an amazing job!

06/24/19 08:25 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="433" phase="goal_identification">Good morning [Name]! Its Monday and time to set your new goal</goal_setting>

06/24/19 08:25 Coach: What would you like your 3rd week SMART goal to be?

06/24/19 09:16 Patient: Good morning [Name]! Yes 

06/24/19 09:39 Coach: You did a great job last week getting 4/4 days for your goal - would you like to increase your steps from last week? 

06/24/19 10:44 Patient: We can try 

06/24/19 10:47 Coach: No pressure! You&apos;ve just been doing so much on average. You had your goal at 2,000 steps, and you were averaging more than 12,000 a day. 

06/24/19 10:47 Coach: What do you think would be good for this week? 

06/24/19 10:49 Patient: 30000

06/24/19 10:50 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="450" phase="goal_refining">Great, and do you want to keep it Monday - Friday?</goal_setting> 

06/24/19 10:51 Patient:  Tuesday- Friday 

06/24/19 10:51 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="451" phase="anticipate_barrier">Okay! last question: How confident are you on a scale of 1 to 10? 1 = not at all, and 10 = absolutely 100%</goal_setting>

06/24/19 10:52 Patient: 8

06/24/19 10:53 Patient: But going to make 10

06/24/19 10:54 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="452" phase="solve_barrier">Okay! If its an 8 we can change it a bit like decrease the steps or the day?</goal_setting> 

06/24/19 10:54 Coach: to make it a 10

06/24/19 10:55 Patient: Make it 10

06/24/19 10:56 Coach: Okie dokes! :) 

06/24/19 10:56 Coach: To write it down: Your week 3 SMART goal is to walk 3,000 steps/ day throughout the day from Tuesday - Friday. 

06/24/19 10:56 Coach: I&apos;ll check in with you at the end of the week. Keep up the amazing work [Name]!

06/24/19 10:58 Patient: Ok 

06/25/19 09:25 Coach: <goal_action gate:gateId="453" phase="follow up">Its a new day! Great job on those steps yesterday [Name]!</goal_action>

06/27/19 09:39 Coach: new record on steps yesterday!! Great job [Name]! 

06/27/19 10:10 Patient: Thank you [Name]

07/01/19 09:40 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="431" phase="goal_identification">Happy Monday [Name]! Its time to set your week 4 goal (half way through!)</goal_setting>

07/01/19 09:40 Coach: You were able to meet your 3,000 step/day goal 5/5 days last week!! GREAT JOB. 

07/01/19 09:41 Coach: What would you like your new goal to be?

07/01/19 17:04 Patient: [Name] I Left my phone at home

07/01/19 22:28 Coach: Good morning [Name], that&apos;s no problem. We can set up the new goal today. 

07/02/19 07:24 Patient: Good morning [Name] what&apos;s new goal today.

07/02/19 09:50 Coach: Hi [Name], last week you set your goa for 3,000 steps a day and you got it 5/5 days

07/02/19 09:51 Coach: You can increase your steps, keep it the same or even decrease it?

07/02/19 10:04 Patient: Keep the same 

07/02/19 10:08 Coach: Okay, so your week 4 goal is to walk 3,000 steps Monday - Friday this week

07/02/19 10:08 Coach: Happy Independence Day!

07/02/19 10:09 Patient: Thank you [Name]! Same to you 

07/08/19 09:44 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="432" phase="goal_identification">Good morning [Name]! Its time to set up your week 5 goal! What would you like your goal to be?</goal_setting> 

07/08/19 09:45 Coach: I know last week was a holiday week so not normal schedule.

07/08/19 09:45 Coach: You had it at 3,000 steps, and you usually average quite a bit more than that. Would you like to make changes, keep the same or decrease?

07/08/19 10:01 Patient: Good morning!We can the same goal

07/08/19 10:11 Coach: Okay, so your week 5 goal will be 3,000 steps Monday - Friday. Thank you!

07/11/19 12:00 Coach: <goal_action gate:gateId="434" phase="follow up">Good morning [Name]! Keep up the good work with those steps!</goal_action>

07/15/19 08:00 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="435" phase="goal_identification">Good morning [Name], its time to create new goal for week 6. What do you think about setting your goal higher - something that is closer to what you have been doing these last 5 weeks?</goal_setting>

07/15/19 10:54 Patient: [Name] l left my Fitbit at home. We can set up something when I get home

07/15/19 10:54 Coach: Sure! No problem

07/16/19 08:46 Coach: Hi [Name]! just checking in. Can we set up your goal today?

07/17/19 08:00 Coach: Hi [Name], its the 3rd day of the week. Don&apos;t want to miss this week&apos;s goal setting. What would you like your goal to be?

07/17/19 08:35 Patient: <goal_setting gate:gateId="436" phase="anticipate_barrier">Good morning [Name]! We can keep the same. Haven&apos;t been feeling my best</goal_setting>

07/17/19 11:18 Coach: Hi [Name], no problem. I&apos;m sorry to hear you haven&apos;t been feeling well. Hope you feel better soon!

07/17/19 11:19 Coach: Okay, so for the 3rd week, since we are already in the middle of the week we can keep the 3,000 steps/day the same and just do it from Wednesday - Friday. Does that sound right?

07/19/19 12:04 Coach: <goal_action gate:gateId="437" phase="follow up">Hi [Name], would you mind manually syncing your fitbit for me? You just need to go to the fitbit app and swipe your finger down. Thank you!</goal_action> 

07/21/19 20:00 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="438" phase="goal_identification">Hi [Name], I&apos;m texting you to set up your 7th fitbit goal a little early since I will be away for part of the week. What would you like your new fitbit goal to be?</goal_setting> 

07/22/19 07:33 Patient: Good morning [Name]! I am on vacation so we can do say goal.

07/22/19 08:24 Coach: Hi [Name]! Okay, so your new goal will be to keep it at 3,000 steps/day during your vacation Monday - Friday. Have fun on your vacation! 

07/22/19 09:04 Patient: Ok thanks! Yes 3,000

07/25/19 07:35 Coach: <goal_action gate:gateId="439" phase="follow up">Hi [Name] if you get a chance can you manually sync your fitbit? You do this by opening the fitbit app and sliding your finger down</goal_action>

07/25/19 08:22 Patient: Good morning [Name]! I think I open up app so what next 

07/25/19 09:38 Coach: Hi [Name], it looks like you figured out and just synced it. Thank you so much! 

07/25/19 09:39 Coach: I have a question: did you wear your fitbit this week? I don&apos;t have any data so I just want to be sure. 

07/25/19 09:41 Patient: No I don&apos;t wear I just put it on today

07/25/19 09:43 Coach: Oh I see. Did you happen to wear it last week? 

07/25/19 09:49 Patient: No 

07/25/19 09:50 Coach: Okay, thanks for confirming. I thought the data was faulty. 

07/25/19 09:52 Coach: I will check in with you at the end of the week to make sure everything is set. Thanks!

07/25/19 09:54 Patient: Ok thanks 

07/26/19 07:00 Coach: Good morning [Name]! This is just a reminder to get your steps in today :) Last day of week 7!

07/26/19 07:07 Patient: Good morning [Name],Ok

07/29/19 07:00 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="440" phase="goal_identification">Good morning [Name]! This is the last week! I was wondering if we could chat a bit about your last week&apos;s goal?</goal_setting> 

07/29/19 07:10 Coach: Could we push ourselves a little bit and maybe shoot for a goal that matches the number of steps you usually walk during the week? For example, during a work week it seems like you walk close to 10,000 steps but you&apos;ve only been setting your goals at 3,000

07/29/19 07:10 Coach: Would you like to set your goal a little higher and finish the last week off with a bang?

07/29/19 07:20 Patient: Good morning  [Name]! Yes I can push for goals this week 

07/29/19 07:22 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="441" phase="goal_refining">Great! So how many steps do you think we could go for this last week?</goal_setting> 

07/29/19 07:28 Patient: We going to push 11,000

07/29/19 07:34 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="442" phase="solve_barrier">Okay, and what will you do to make sure you reach that goal?</goal_setting> 

07/29/19 07:49 Patient: Walk 

07/29/19 07:51 Coach: Lets be a little more specific - for example if you realize by the end of the work day that you haven&apos;t reached your goal yet, do you have a plan to make sure you get those steps in at home? 

07/29/19 07:51 Coach: Or for example, will you put some extra steps in throughout the work day during your break, etc? 

07/29/19 08:04 Patient: Yes not at work today! Be back tomorrow.

07/29/19 08:05 Coach: <goal_setting gate:gateId="443" phase="anticipate_barrier">Okay last 2 questions: 1) will you start 11,000 steps today and until Friday? and then 2) how confident are you with reaching your goal? (scale of 1-10)</goal_setting>

07/29/19 08:07 Patient: Yes I will start today! I&apos;m confident scale 10

07/29/19 08:43 Coach: Great! So your last goal is to walk 11,000 steps Monday - Friday this week. I will check in with you on Monday. 

07/29/19 08:43 Coach: Sorry Wednesday*

07/31/19 09:00 Coach: <goal_action gate:gateId="444" phase="follow up">Hi [Name]! How is this last week going so far?</goal_action>

07/31/19 10:41 Patient: It&apos;s good 

08/01/19 13:57 Coach: Hi [Name]!! Just want to say I&apos;m impressed by those numbers!! You&apos;re doing an amazing job :) Second to last day of the week and the study! Keep it up

08/01/19 14:51 Patient: Ok

